<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World, Deadbeef!</string>

    <string name="app_name">DeaDBeeF Pro</string>



    <string name="service_name">org.deadbeef.android.mediaservice</string>
    <string name="title_file_browser">Browse file</string>
    <string name="playback_service_connected">Connected</string>
    <string name="playback_service_disconnected">Disconnected</string>
    <string name="playback_service_started">Disconnected</string>
    <string name="playback_service_stopped">Stopped</string>
    <string name="playback_service_label">Deadbeef</string>
<string name="ctx_menu_add_files">Add file(s)</string>
<string name="ctx_menu_add_folder">Add folder</string>
<string name="ctx_menu_remove">Remove from playlist</string>
<string name="ctx_menu_move_to_playlist">Move to another playlist</string>
<string name="ctx_menu_properties">Properties</string>
<string name="new_playlist">Create new playlist</string>

<string name="alert_dialog_ok">OK</string>
<string name="alert_dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>
<string name="rename_playlist">Rename playlist</string>
<string name="delete_playlist">Delete playlist</string>
<string name="delete_playlist_confirm">Sure?</string>
<string name="about">About</string>
<string name="about_text">

DeaDBeeF Pro 1.0.7dev\n



Copyright © 2009-2011 <a href="mailto:wakeroid@gmail.com">Alexey Yakovenko</a>\n
<a href="http://deadbeef.sf.net">http://deadbeef.sf.net</a>\n
\n
This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,\n
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of\n
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
</string>
<color name="expanding_child_background">#ff404040</color>
<string name="widget_initial_text">Touch to select music.</string>
<string name="title_playlist_viewer">Playlist</string>
<string name="title_eq">Equalizer</string>
<string name="new_eq_preset">New EQ preset</string>
<string name="delete_eq_preset">Delete EQ preset</string>
<string name="delete_eq_preset_confirm">Sure?</string>
<string name="rename_eq_preset">Rename EQ preset</string>
<string name="select_eq_preset">EQ Presets</string>
<string name="add_location">Add location</string>
<string name="osslicenses_button">Open source licenses</string>
<string name="osslicenses_text">
<b>libcurl</b>\n
COPYRIGHT AND PERMISSION NOTICE\n
\n
Copyright (c) 1996 - 2010, Daniel Stenberg, &lt;daniel@haxx.se&gt;.\n
\n
All rights reserved.\n
\n
Permission to use, copy, modify, and distribute this software for any purpose\n
with or without fee is hereby granted, provided that the above copyright\n
notice and this permission notice appear in all copies.\n
\n
THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR\n
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,\n
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS. IN\n
NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM,\n
DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR\n
OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE\n
OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.\n
\n
Except as contained in this notice, the name of a copyright holder shall not\n
be used in advertising or otherwise to promote the sale, use or other dealings\n
in this Software without prior written authorization of the copyright holder.\n
\n
<b>DUMB</b>\n
Dynamic Universal Music Bibliotheque, Version 0.9.3\n
\n
Copyright (C) 2001-2005 Ben Davis, Robert J Ohannessian and Julien Cugniere\n
\n
This software is provided \'as-is\', without any express or implied warranty.\n
In no event shall the authors be held liable for any damages arising from the\n
use of this software.\n
\n
Permission is granted to anyone to use this software for any purpose,\n
including commercial applications, and to alter it and redistribute it\n
freely, subject to the following restrictions:\n
\n
1. The origin of this software must not be misrepresented; you must not claim\n
   that you wrote the original software. If you use this software in a\n
   product, you are requested to acknowledge its use in the product\n
   documentation, along with details on where to get an unmodified version of\n
   this software, but this is not a strict requirement.\n
\n
   [Note that the above point asks for a link to DUMB, not just a mention.\n
   Googling for DUMB doesn\'t help much! The URL is "http://dumb.sf.net/".]\n
\n
   [The link was originally strictly required. This was changed for two\n
   reasons. Firstly, if many projects request an acknowledgement, the list of\n
   acknowledgements can become quite unmanageable. Secondly, DUMB was placing\n
   a restriction on the code using it, preventing people from using the GNU\n
   General Public Licence which disallows any such restrictions. See\n
   http://www.gnu.org/philosophy/bsd.html for more information on this\n
   subject. However, if DUMB plays a significant part in your project, we do\n
   urge you to acknowledge its use.]\n
\n
2. Altered source versions must be plainly marked as such, and must not be\n
   misrepresented as being the original software.\n
\n
3. This notice may not be removed from or altered in any source distribution.\n
\n
4. If you are using the Program in someone else\'s bedroom on any Monday at\n
   3:05 pm, you are not allowed to modify the Program for ten minutes. [This\n
   clause provided by Inphernic; every licence should contain at least one\n
   clause, the reasoning behind which is far from obvious.]\n
\n
5. Users who wish to use DUMB for the specific purpose of playing music are\n
   required to feed their dog on every full moon (if deemed appropriate).\n
   [This clause provided by Allefant, who couldn\'t remember what Inphernic\'s\n
   clause was.]\n
\n
6. No clause in this licence shall prevent this software from being depended\n
   upon by a product licensed under the GNU General Public Licence. If such a\n
   clause is deemed to exist, Debian, then it shall be respected in spirit as\n
   far as possible and all other clauses shall continue to apply in full\n
   force.\n
\n
We regret that we cannot provide any warranty, not even the implied warranty\n
of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.\n
\n
Some files generated or copied by automake, autoconf and friends are\n
available in an extra download. These fall under separate licences but are\n
all free to distribute. Please check their licences as necessary.\n
\n
<b>FLAC</b>\n
Copyright (C) 2000,2001,2002,2003,2004,2005,2006,2007 Josh Coalson\n
\n
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without\n
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions\n
are met:\n
\n
- Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright\n
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n
\n
- Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright\n
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the\n
documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\n
\n
- Neither the name of the Xiph.org Foundation nor the names of its\n
contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from\n
this software without specific prior written permission.\n
\n
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS\n
``AS IS\'\' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT\n
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR\n
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE FOUNDATION OR\n
CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL,\n
EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO,\n
PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR\n
PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF\n
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING\n
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS\n
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\n
\n
<b>libogg, libvorbis</b>\n
Copyright (c) 2002, Xiph.org Foundation\n
\n
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without\n
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions\n
are met:\n
\n
- Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright\n
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n
\n
- Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright\n
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the\n
documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\n
\n
- Neither the name of the Xiph.org Foundation nor the names of its\n
contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from\n
this software without specific prior written permission.\n
\n
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS\n
``AS IS\'\' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT\n
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR\n
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE FOUNDATION\n
OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,\n
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT\n
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,\n
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY\n
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT\n
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE\n
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\n
\n
<b>wavpack</b>\n
\n
               Copyright (c) 1998 - 2009 Conifer Software\n
                          All rights reserved.\n
\n
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without\n
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:\n
\n
    * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice,\n
      this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n
    * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice,\n
      this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the\n
      documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\n
    * Neither the name of Conifer Software nor the names of its contributors\n
      may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software\n
      without specific prior written permission.\n
\n
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS"\n
AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE\n
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE\n
ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE REGENTS OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR\n
ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL\n
DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR\n
SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER\n
CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY,\n
OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE\n
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\n
\n
<b>libzip</b>\n
Copyright (C) 1999-2008 Dieter Baron and Thomas Klausner\n
The authors can be contacted at &lt;libzip@nih.at&gt;\n
\n
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without\n
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions\n
are met:\n
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright\n
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright\n
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in\n
   the documentation and/or other materials provided with the\n
   distribution.\n
3. The names of the authors may not be used to endorse or promote\n
   products derived from this software without specific prior\n
   written permission.\n
\n
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AUTHORS ``AS IS\'\' AND ANY EXPRESS\n
OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED\n
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE\n
ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY\n
DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL\n
DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE\n
GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS\n
INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER\n
IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR\n
OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN\n
IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\n
\n
<b>musepack</b>\n
Copyright (c) 2005-2009, The Musepack Development Team\n
All rights reserved.\n
\n
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without\n
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are\n
met:\n
\n
* Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright\n
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n
\n
* Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above\n
copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following\n
disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided\n
with the distribution.\n
\n
* Neither the name of the The Musepack Development Team nor the\n
names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote\n
products derived from this software without specific prior\n
written permission.\n
\n
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS\n
"AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT\n
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR\n
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT\n
OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,\n
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT\n
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,\n
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY\n
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT\n
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE\n
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\n
\n
<b>tta</b>\n
\n
Copyright (c) 2004 True Audio Software. All rights reserved.\n
\n
\n
\n
\n
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without\n
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions\n
are met:\n
\n
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright\n
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright\n
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the\n
   documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\n
3. Neither the name of the True Audio Software nor the names of its\n
   contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived\n
   from this software without specific prior written permission.\n
\n
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS\n
"AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT\n
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR\n
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT\n
OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,\n
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT\n
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,\n
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY\n
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT\n
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE\n
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\n

</string>

<string name="buyfull_text">Please buy full version to get access to this feature</string>
<string name="remove_track_confirm">Are you sure?</string>
</resources>
